

CONTACT

- +254-725-406-004
- Nairobi, Kenya
- https://aogajoseph.github.i o/Personal-Website/

EDUCATION

2018 - Present ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY

Certificate, Full-stack
 JavaScript

April, 2008

INTRO-TECH COMPUTER COLLEGE

Certificate in IT

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- NPM
- Github

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Leadership

JOSEPH ONYANGO

WEB DEVELOPER, DIGITAL STRATEGIST & WEB CONSULTANT

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a passionate professional in web development and digital strategy, bringing a unique blend of technical skills and strategic insight to help people and enterprises thrive in the digital age. I specialize in using technology to meet specific needs and drive growth, efficiency and innovation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Zero to Mastery Academy

Volunteer, Web Developer

2018 - PRESENT

- Taking part in coding challenges, collaboratively.
- · Performing coding tasks.
- Contributing to open-source projects.

Spina-bifida & Hydrocephalus Association of Kenya (SHAK)

2020- 2023

Web Developer

Enhanced daily operations by designing and building digital tools that significantly boosted efficiency and overall productivity.

Vivo Energies, Kenya.Total Service Station, Likoni road.

2010-2020

Customer Service Attendant

Ensured customer satisfaction by providing information, resolving complaints, processing transactions, maintaining records, conducting sales and managing inquiries.

FUTURE LEARNING

- · Advanced JavaScript.
- · NodeJS for Back-end scripting.
- SQL and NoSQL Databases.
- CI/CD Pipelines and Automation.
- Al and Machine Learning.
- · Advanced Cloud Computing.
- · Design Thinking.
- Technopreneurship.